The ocean is one of the largest graveyards in human history.
But if there's one thing more disturbing than the geese buried in the water, it's the ships that refuse to sink but swallow everyone on it.
Dragged alone on the horizon, its hull resists the waves, but on its deck, not a single living sound is heard.
That's exactly what happened in 1955 when the pacific okemus became infinite blue.
An unsinked ship has been found remaining on the water.
However, all 25 people on the ship disappeared without a trace.
This is the story of the fruit coyta.
It's one of the darkest, most unresolved, and the greatest ghost ship mysteries in the history of the sea that time can't forget.
Welcome to Sado Arcirea.
The star's buzz star, transportation and trade between islands south of the Pacific okemus have been difficult and stringed high throughout history.
The bonds between the blockage are largely based on small ships of commerce and passenger ships that travel through these waters.
Tokella's ability to trace from land to high places is not only a means of transportation, but foam as well as foam with the outside world.
Mevve coyta was one of the ships that made the geography or the expedition.
In the terms of the period, life was important to the people and the people of the region and to those who served on the island.
Some of the routes and services of geography were surrounded by heat and deep water from the Pacific.
But one of the burutin sea journeys would be the beginning of a dark event that would be carved into southern pacific history.
A group of 25 people sailed among the starships, along with their journeys and their crews.
The profiler on the ship was very diverse, traveling among the islands, a place as young as the mirettebat of the people who were acting as the general.
One of the most remarkable names was a bottomless doctor from England's derbite.
At this time in his life, the derbili doctor had been part of this journey in the Pacific.
However, the journey did not go as planned.
The ship did not reach its destination, we were cut off from sea communication, and the mevecoyta disappeared into the darkness of the Pacific without a trace or a moan behind it.
Twenty-five people walked into the open sea with no witnesses and no clues left behind.
A ship was spotted drifting in the Pacific Ocean after days of indistinctness.
That was the missing mevecoyta.
When the ship was found, the first truth that baffled researchers and sailors was revealed that the mevecoyta was still on the water.
There was no debris that sank, or collapsed at the bottom of the ocean.
The ship didn't sink, and it kept swimming.
But when it reached the deck, it was faced with the dissolution of reality.
Not a single human on the ship.
25 passengers and all crews were destroyed.
The crew had no sign of the sinking, no sign of the passengers.
The fact that the ship was able to swim to its surface turned the question of why and how the people on it were separated into a gigantic riddle.
How could he have lost every day on a boat that continued to swim?
Starstar, the fact that the mevecoyta is abandoned has caused a massive shock wave in the region.
It immediately took on an international dimension.
This tragedy directly related to Tokella,
He's found a large intrinsically and integrated ralph.
For the victims of the death or disappearance of Mevecoyita in tragedy, in the middle of nowhere.
A memorial grandkid was organized.
Families and public opinion were in deep mourning.
But besides that grief, you deserved a great deal of anger and lack of answers.
The real deal is that the Tokella ucoyita tragedy,
Fesme accompanied calls for a forensic prosecution and a trial to investigate what killed them.
Authorities and families demanded that the truth behind this disaster be revealed.
Britain has been asked to resolve the mystery perlem behind 25 missing persons, including the family and relatives of the derbil doctor.
However, the study of my part was not able to provide any concrete evidence of where 25 people had gone.
Over the years, the star house has been listed among history's chilling ghost ships in meve coita, media and research publications.
The world's mysterious and research mecas have assessed this on the same floor as Mari Celeste's greatest unresolved marine foods.
There have been numerous allegations and theories as to why the ship was abandoned.
The fact that a ship leaves its ship in a sinking state usually suggests panic, emergency management failures, or an unknown threat from the outside.
In the naval history, the ship will sink, but the ship will float, while the ship will float, it will have human specimens floating in the ocean.
In the case of meve coita, however, none of these theories have been officially confirmed.
The reason the ship was abandoned, or the fate of 25 people, we have no conclusive claims or confirmed paintings.
The theories have been presented as conclusive evidence of nothing but speculation.
The facts we know for certain about the Meve coita incident today are these.
Firstly, meve coita was found floating abandoned in the Pacific Ocean.
Secondly, when the ship was found, it was still on the water and it didn't sink.
All 25 people found in the ship have disappeared and have never been heard from again.
The fourth ride is related to the tokela, and among the victims is a curative doctor.
Following the fifth incident, a pick-up ceremony was held for the victims in the new zelanda, and a formal hearing was called in.
These are our limits, an assumption that doesn't prove to every narrative beyond the facts.
A star star, who couldn't find a burn in the story of Mele coita, remains inconsolable despite the past six years.
If the ship isn't sinking and can keep swimming, why did 25 people leave this safe zone?
What was it that required you to abandon a technique that continued to swim in the open sea and stay on the shore of the ocean?
He's got a stable doctor and 24 other people on board.
Most importantly, there was never a single reason why 25 souls were lost from a ship that was still floating.
The Pacific Ocean continues to keep the secret of the Meve coita deep inside.
Sado Arce and thank you for watching.
Don't leave the questions in your mind in the dark, remember to float and follow.